好好走路  别跑  巴克
Walk, don't run, Barker.
史密斯  华盛顿和杰斐逊
Smith, how many slaves
有多少奴隶
did Washington and Jefferson have?
帮帮我吧
Oh, come on.
就这一次
Just this once?
我发誓
I promise.
华盛顿有300个
Washington had 300,
杰斐逊有600个
Jefferson 600.
上帝保佑美国
God bless America.
托马斯  今天你来领誓言
Thomas, you'll lead the Pledge today.
好的  老师
Yes, sir.
全班起立
Class, rise.
我发誓我将遵纪守法
I swear I will observe the law,
全力履行我在家中和在学校的义务
conscientiously fulfill my duties at home and school,
忠诚且忠顺
be faithful and obedient
并宣誓拥护纳粹帝国的元首
and pledge absolute allegiance until death
阿道夫·希特勒
to the leader of the Nazi Empire
至死不渝
Adolf Hitler.
胜利万岁  胜利万岁  胜利万岁
Sieg heil! Sieg heil! Sieg heil!
你没事吧
You all right?
没事  我很好
Yeah, yeah, I'm fine.
这是我家人
It's my family.
你真是个幸运的人
Lucky guy.
是啊
Yeah.
人总要有为之奋斗的人  不是吗
A fella's got to work for something, right?
你们修好无线电了吗
Did you guys get that radio working yet?
还没有
Not yet.
介意我自己看看吗
Mind if I take a look at it myself?
你急什么  朋友
What's the rush, friend?
有个送我上船的朋友
There's a gal who got me on the boat.
我需要  确定她没事
I need to... make sure she's okay.
我们会修好无线电的
We'll get that radio working.
你不用担心
Don't you worry.
- 他来了  - 谁
- He's coming. - Who?
给我们指令的人
The guy we answer to.
你为什么那么做  朱莉安娜
Why did you do it, Juliana?
你爱上他了  是不是
You're in love with him? Is that it?
他们会需要一个理由的  朱莉安娜
They're going to need a reason, Juliana,
一个能让人信服的理由
a good one.
我不能
I couldn't--
我不能杀掉他  卡伦
I couldn't take his life, Karen.
我也不能让你杀掉他
I couldn't let you, either.
弗兰克在哪里
Where's Frank?
我不知道
I don't know.
告诉他有人枪击了皇太子
I told him someone shot the Crown Prince,
然后他就跑掉了  我不知道他去哪了
then he ran off, I don't know where.
所以呢
Well?
她只是  她只是下不了手
She just couldn't-- She just couldn't do it.
我不认为她是想
I don't think she meant--
她想怎样不重要
Doesn't matter what the hell she meant.
莱姆
Lem.
不是吗
Does it?
你知道我的  莱姆
You know me, Lem.
是啊  我太懂你了
Yeah. I know you.
我不认为他会伤害你
I don't believe he'd hurt you,
伤害你们任何一个
any of you.
我们需要那卷影片
We needed that film.
她知道的
She knew it.
你们都没看那个影片  我看了
None of you watched that film. I did.
你带我去见高堡奇人
You take me to the Man in the High Castle.
带我去  然后我可以一帧一帧地描述给他听
Take me and I can describe it to him frame by frame.
你是吃了熊心豹子胆了
You've got a lot of goddamn nerve.
问他  问他想不想见我
Ask him. Ask him if he wants to see me.
已经问过了
Already did.
你想要录口供吗  弗林克先生
You wish to make a statement, Mr. Frink?
你知道艾德·麦卡锡
You know Ed McCarthy...
没有枪击皇太子
didn't shoot the Crown Prince.
在你杀了我姐姐
I had to do something after--
和她的孩子们以后
after you killed my sister...
我必须得做点什么
and her kids.
所以你枪击皇太子来复仇吗
So you shot him as an act of revenge?
你知道是的
You know I did.
将军已抵达
The general has arrived.
你不准备逮捕我吗
Aren't you going to arrest me?
你没有枪击皇太子
You did not shoot the Crown Prince.
你作为一个犹太人  你知道我不需要理由
As a Jew, you know I need no charges
就可以让你死
to order your death.
是  是  我知道
Yeah. Yeah, I know.
那么你就接受你朋友的认罪证词吧
Then you will accept your friend's confession.
认罪证词
Confession?
他认罪了吗
He confessed?
是我做的  好吗
I did it, okay?
是我做的
I did it.
这样  听着
Okay, look--
是我做的  好吗  是我
I did it, all right? I did it.
该死的人是我
I'm the one who's supposed to die.
行吗  求你了
Okay? Please.
该死的人是我
I'm the one who's supposed to die.
小野田将军
General Onoda.
我相信您的旅途很愉快
I trust you had a pleasant journey.
这是我战后第一次来美国
My first time on American soil since the war,
木户台一
Kido Tai-i.
改变很大啊
Much has changed.
确实是
Indeed.
我们要出去  你我两个人
We must go out, you and I,
去看看到底改变了多少
to see just how much.
我知道北滩区
I understand the North Beach area
有很多绝佳的女招待酒吧
has excellent hostess bars.
我是这么听说的
So I have been told.
你的副官告诉我有值得庆祝的事情
Your sergeant tells me there's cause to celebrate.
你抓到了皇太子枪击事件的嫌疑人
You have a suspect in the shooting of the Crown Prince.
调查还未结束
The investigation is not yet complete,
但是是的  案子明天会呈上
but yes. The case will be presented tomorrow.
很好
Excellent.
还有你们在追查一部
And a film you were pursuing
来自高堡奇人的影片
from the Man in the High Castle.
影片落入黑社会之手了
It fell into the hands of the Yakuza.
我们
We--
我追丢了
I lost it.
不论如何  我们都该庆祝一下
We shall celebrate, nonetheless.
不要使太大劲压
Don't press too hard.
小范围地来回滚就好
Just short strokes back and forth.
就是这样
That's it.
妈妈  外面有辆车
Mom, there's a car outside.
我去看看
Uh....I'll go see.
你和艾米待着  好吗
Stay with Amy, okay?
看到了吗  我没事
You see? I'm fine.
毫发无损
Just fine.
你还好吗
You all right?
发生什么了
What happened?
海德里希在他该在的地方  监狱里
Heydrich's in prison, where he belongs.
他会被审问
He'll be questioned...
然后作为叛徒被处于绞刑
and hanged as a traitor.
所以都结束了
So it's over.
海德里希在柏林有同谋
Heydrich has allies in Berlin:
那些人准备要背叛元首
men prepared to betray the Führer,
和他一样
just as he was.
你得逮捕他们
You have to arrest them.
如果我们知道是哪些人  我们就会的
We would if we knew who they were.
我们不能确定  而这些人非常危险
We can't be sure, and these men are very dangerous.
所以
So...
你现在可以
you can now...
把枪还给我了
You can give me that gun back now.
怎么了
Hey.
What is it?
我知道你指望我坚强
I know that you count on me to be strong.
你确实很坚强啊  你是我知道的最坚强的人
You are strong. You're the strongest person I know.
当我想到要对我们的孩子们开枪的时候
When I thought about turning that gun on our children--
如果刚刚下车的人是海德里希
If Heydrich had pulled up in that car instead of me--
我知道  我知道
I know that. I know that.
但是我不能
But I couldn't have--
我们的孩子们  我做不到
Our children-- I couldn't have.
明白
Understood.
所以你们修好无线电了啊
You got that radio working, huh?
你他妈是个纳粹
You're a goddamn Nazi.
影片  交出来
The film. Hand it over.
这个吗
This film.
你敢放手  你就是个死人了
If you drop that, you're dead.
为了这卷片子  抵抗组织给你们多少钱
How much is the Resistance going to pay you for it?
五万
50,000.
听着  你们被骗了
Look, you guys are being cheated.
黑社会的卖价是那两倍
The Yakuza sold it for twice that,
并且我得告诉你们  我不认为抵抗组织有那么多钱
and I got to tell you I don't think the Resistance has the money.
放屁
Bullshit.
听着  你们需要钱  对吗
Look, you guys need cash. Am I right?
来养活你们的家人
To support your families.
不是吗  这就是为什么你们把像我这样的人偷渡到墨西哥
Come on, that's why you smuggle people like me down to Mexico.
- 你想说什么  - 闭嘴
- What's your point? - Shut up.
我不是纳粹
I'm not a Nazi.
但是我要把这卷片子卖给他们
But I am selling this film to them,
其实你们也可以大赚一笔
and there can be a lot of money in this for you, too.
一大笔钱
A lot of money.
- 多少  - 我说了闭嘴
- How much? - I said shut up.
二十万日元
200,000 yen.
每人二十万日元
200,000 each.
我才是那个本该死的人
I'm the one who's supposed to die.
贸易部长在哪
Where is the Trade Minister?
我不知道  总督察
I don't know, Chief Inspector.
战后我一直没能联系上他
I have been unable to reach him since the--
我在这里
I am here.
您  还好吗  贸易部长
Are you...quite all right, Trade Minister?
从这场战争以来
Since the war,
我们和纳粹党的联盟一直不稳定
we have shared an uneasy alliance with the Nazis.
现在元首病了
Now the Führer is ill,
他的人吹嘘自己的意志力
and his men boast of their will...
我们清楚我们必须在他们进攻之前进攻
We know we must strike before they strike.
过来拿你的热狗
Get your hotdogs right here!
我们拿到了苹果蜜饯
We got candied apples and...
现在我们进了虎穴
Today we enter the tiger's cave.
我们进去是因为两周前
We enter it because two weeks ago
科学部长志村在他的口袋里发现了一个盒子
Science Minister Shimura found a capsule in his pocket,
盒子里面有一个从柏林的帝国研究委员会
and inside the capsule was microfilm
走私过来的微缩胶片
smuggled from the Reich Research Council in Berlin.
微缩胶片里的内容已经被确认
The contents of the microfilm has been confirmed.
总算  我们也拥有了
At long last, we, too, possess the data
能够建立海森堡设备的数据了
to build a Heisenberg device.
当设备创建完成时
When it is completed,
必须在北美纳粹党
the device must be in range
瞄准纽约市的
of North American Nazi targets...
目标范围内
of New York City.
这是属于我们的时刻
This is our moment.
我们必须毫不犹豫的抓住它
We must not hesitate to seize it.
贸易部长
Trade Minister.
我几乎可以肯定你已经和那位纳粹党上校
I am all but certain you have passed those plans
把那些计划交给科学部长了
to the Science Minister with that Nazi colonel.
你是过来逮捕我的吗  总督察
Are you here to arrest me, Chief Inspector?
贸易部长  我知道这正是你所期望的
Trade Minister, I know that this is what you wish,
而且你看起来好像  很困扰
and yet you seem... troubled.
我期望能和纳粹党平权
I wish for parity with the Nazis,
来平衡权力  维护和平
to balance the power, to maintain the peace.
你已经听将军说了  战争不可避免
You heard the general. War is inevitable.
或许吧
Possibly.
但是有了这样一个武器
But with a weapon like this...
这样的战争怎么会赢呢
how can such a war be won?
把它打开吧
Let's open it up.
那就是这场交易的结果了
That's their end of the bargain.
带他离开这里  斯利姆
Get him out of here, Slim.
不要把它们都花在一个地方了  孩子们
Don't spend it all in one place, boys.
谢谢  兄弟
Thank you, man.
很高兴见到你
Am I glad to see you.
让我们带你去纽约吧
Let's get you to New York.
好的
Okay.
给  给  给  给  给
Here, here, here, here.
- 我的包呢  - 你的包在这
- Where's my bag? - Here's your bag.
快点  船长
Come on, Captain.
快点  杰克  快点回来
Come on, Jack, let's get back fast.
早上好  上校
Good morning, Obergruppenführer.
克里姆少校
Major Klemm.
邓肯上校
Obergruppenführer Duncan
很想与你谈话  长官
is eager to speak with you, sir.
乔·布莱克已经上报情况了吗
Has Joe Blake reported in?
他现在正在你办公室等你
He's waiting in your office now.
乔
Joe.
恭喜
Congratulations.
我很高兴
I'm very pleased.
怎么了  乔
Something wrong, Joe?
你告诉我你会给那些人报酬的
You told me you'd pay those men.
他们是罪犯  乔
They were criminals, Joe.
他们是想让你死的罪犯  你应该毫无同情才对
Criminals who wanted you dead. You should feel no remorse.
朱莉安娜·科伦怎么样了
What about Juliana Crain?
她死了
Oh, she's dead.
几乎确定了
Almost certainly.
已经快24个小时了  乔
It's been nearly 24 hours, Joe.
你已经证明了自身的可靠性
You've proved yourself capable,
但是未来
but in the future
你必须学会控制你的感情
you have to learn to keep your feelings in check.
我做不到  长官
I can't do that, sir.
是吗
Oh, you can't?
我想要辞职
I'd like to resign.
你辞不了职的  乔
You don't get to resign, Joe.
- 你已经拿到了你的胶片  - 没错
- You got your film. - Yes.
对元首极其重要的胶片
A film of great importance to the Führer.
想想那意味着什么吧  乔
Think about what that means, Joe.
想想你父亲会有多为你骄傲
Think how proud your father will be.
我父亲甚至都不知道我在为你工作
My father doesn't even know I work for you.
他当然知道了
Oh, of course he does.
现在  我困住你
Now, I stuck with you...
是因为我一直相信
because I always believed
等时机到的时候
that when the time came,
你会去做必须做的事
you'd do what had to be done.
这不是我想要成为的人
This isn't the man I want to be.
这不是你想成为的人吗
This isn't the man you wanted to be?
我明白了
I see.
看来我看错你了  乔
Well, it seems I misjudged you, Joe.
克里姆少校  我去柏林的航班是什么时候
Major Klemm, what time is my flight to Berlin?
一小时后起飞  长官
It leaves in an hour, sir.
我现在可以走吗
Can I go now?
可以  你可以走了
Yes, you can go.
你想见我  是吗  贸易部长
You wish to see me, Trade Minister?
你之前告诉我不要失去希望
You told me before to not lose hope.
我应该继续冥想
That I should keep meditating.
我希望冥想能给您带来平静
I hoped meditation might bring you peace,
正如它带给我的一样
as it does me.
仅此而已吗
And nothing more.
我去了公园冥想
I went to the park to meditate.
但它并没由给我带来平静
But it did not bring me peace.
它把我
It brought me...
带到了一个奇怪的地方
to a strange place.
那是旧金山
It was San Francisco
但不是这个旧金山
but not this San Francisco.
那个旧金山被美国人统治着
It was ruled by Americans...
自由自在的走着  大喊着
walking freely, shouting...
笑着
and laughing.
您是梦到了过去
You had a dream of the past.
不  不是
No. No.
那不是过去
It wasn't the past.
那感觉起来根本不像是一个梦
And it didn't feel like a dream.
联系一下皇妃
Get a hold of the Crown Princess.
告诉她我有紧急要务要处理
Tell her that I have an urgent matter to discuss.
朱莉安娜
Juliana.
朱莉安娜  嘿
Juliana. Hey.
阿诺德
Arnold.
你怎么了
What happened to you?
只是发生了个意外
I just had an accident.
你不想让伤口感染吧
You don't want to get that infected.
- 过来  我来帮你  - 我不需要你的帮忙
- Come on, let me help you. - I don't need your help.
- 你是一个人吗  - 是啊  我一个人
- Are you alone? - Yeah, I'm alone.
听着  你们  你们离开的那么急
Listen, you guys, you left in such a hurry,
我是想过来确认一下有没有事
I wanted to make sure everything was okay.
朱尔斯哪去了
Where's Jules?
她走了
She's gone.
她走了是什么意思
What's that supposed to mean, she's gone?
意思就是她已经离开这里了
It means she had to get out of here.
她安全吗
Is she safe?
不  不是要跟你道谢
No, no thanks to you.
我也不知道到底是什么意思
I don't know what that's supposed to mean, either.
你为他们工作了多久  阿诺德
How long have you worked for them, Arnold?
在日本政府大厦
In the Nippon Building?
你怎么能这样做  你怎么会心安理得
How can you do it? How could you live with yourself?
监视你自己的人  你到底是什么样的人啊
Spying on your own people? What kind of man are you?
一个要照顾他家人的人
The kind of man that takes care of his family.
- 我努力来帮过  - 你没有照顾好你的家人
- I tried to help-- - You didn't take care of your family.
是你让特鲁迪死了的
You got Trudy killed.
我去你妈的  弗兰克
God damn you, Frank.
我没有害死我的女儿
I did not get my daughter killed.
- 我尽力去帮过她  - 你他妈就是个日本人
- I tried to help her. - You're a fucking Pon.
这个艾德有关  是吧
This is about Ed, isn't it?
你知道艾德什么
What do you know about Ed?
我就在监听室  弗兰克
I'm in a listening room, Frank.
我听到了一切
I hear everything.
我在电话里听到了他祖父
I heard his grandfather on the phone.
阿诺德  你要帮他
Arnold, you got to help him.
我帮不了他  没人帮得了他
I cannot help him. Nobody can help him.
拜托   宪兵队已经抓到他了
Come on. The Kempeitai's got him.
- 弗兰克  - 宪兵队
- Frank-- - The Kempeitai.
我尽力帮过我自己的女儿  但看看最后发生了什么
I tried to help my own daughter, and look what happened.
- 拜托  - 你得放手了
- Oh, come on. - You got to leave this alone.
你需要
You'll need to--
你需要找一个日本人
You need to find a Pon.
一个人脉广的人
Somebody well connected.
我不认识任何人脉广的日本人
I don't know any well connected Pons.
那去就找一个人脉广的人
Then find someone who does.
诶  诶  诶  弗林克先生
Well, well, well, Mr. Frink.
你重新考虑好了吗
Have you reconsidered?
重新考虑
Reconsidered?
是啊  我的提议啊
Yeah, my offer
和我的日本客户一起
to place some more authentic Americana
放置一些更真实的美国文物
with my Japanese clientele.
听着  你遇到麻烦了  我们都遇上麻烦了
Listen, you got a problem. We both do.
什么麻烦
What sort of problem?
我的一个朋友因射杀皇太子
A friend of mine's been arrested
被逮捕了
for shooting the Crown Prince.
然后逼迫他认罪
Then forced him to confess.
所以那和我有什么关系
So what does that have to do with me?
他被抓时身上带着一把枪
He was caught with a gun.
上膛的子弹是你的
The shells in the chamber were yours.
不好意思  但是我必须得关门了
Sumimasen, but I must close.
有一位生病的阿姨  不好意思
Uh, uh, a sick aunt. Sumimasen.
不好意思
Sumimasen.
- 你做了什么  - 我朋友是无辜的
- What have you done? - My friend's not guilty.
在他们过来杀我之前只是时间问题了
It's only a matter of time before they come for me to kill me.
你一定认识一些有钱的日本客人
You must have some wealthy Japanese clients.
如果是的话怎样
So what if I do?
如果你可以的话  我不知道
Well, if you could-- I don't know--
跟他们谈
talk to one of them,
让他们牵线搭桥
get him to pull some strings.
牵线搭桥  你有病吗
Pull some st-- Are you out of your mind?
别这样  我只是想帮你
Come on. I'm just trying to help you.
帮我  那是因为你  弗兰克先生
Help me? It's because of you, Mr. Frink,
我死定了
I'm a dead man.
是的  你会死定的
Yeah, you will be a dead man
除非我们找到方法让我的朋友离开这
unless we find a way to get my friend out of this.
镇静剂的功效如何
How's that sedative treating you?
我需要一些喝的
Mm. I need something to drink.
拼图
Puzzles.
那么多拼图
So many puzzles.
而你是
And you are...
漂亮的一块
just another pretty piece.
我死了
I was dead.
可能是吧
Maybe you are.
你说的是什么意思
What's that supposed to mean?
事实跟死亡一样可怕
Truth is as terrible as death.
但更难找
But harder to find.
你有脑子不太正常
You have an unnatural mind.
你知道吗
Are you aware of that?
你已经有一个了
You already got one.
对
Right.
噢
Ohh.
我在哪里
Where am I?
你回答我的问题  姑娘
You answer my questions, chickie,
而不是问别的
not the other way around.
你明白吗
You understand?
明白
Yeah.
跟我来
Come with me.
59, 60...
你就是他  对吧
You're him, aren't you?
我是阿本德森  豪索尔尼·阿本德森
I'm Abendsen, Hawthorn Abendsen.
这是你的城堡
This is your castle.
这是我的城堡  就在这里
This is my castle right here,
有意识和无意识的头脑
the conscious and unconscious mind,
灵魂
the psyche.
卡尔·荣格  知道吗
Karl Jung. Got it?
那是家庭电影
That's a home movie.
7月4日在菲尼克斯的烟火
4th of July fireworks in Phoenix.
1961年7月4日  不可能
4th of July in 1961. It's not possible.
但那就是
But it is.
你正拿着它
You're holding it.
告诉我你看到过的影片
Tell me about the film you saw.
它很像新闻影片
It's like a newsreel.
我从未见过如此
I've never seen anything so...
荒凉的景象  那是  那是旧金山
desolate. It was-- It was San Francisco,
但那全都毁灭了
but it was all ruins.
我可以认出金门大桥
I can make out the Golden Gate Bridge.
那里有一些受害者的影子
There were shadows of some of the victims.
他们就像
They were like...
像烧着了
like burns.
那是
It was--
结局
The end.
人们怎么了
What about people?
- 他们怎么了  - 在爆炸之后
- What about them? - Did you see any
你有见到任何人吗  说吧
after the explosion? Come on.
有男人被纳粹士兵列队
There were men lined up by Nazi soldiers.
看起来和他们在一起的还有
They looked like they were with the Resistance--
- 抵抗组织的游击队员  - 有多少
- partisans-- - How many?
10个  可能是12个
Ten, maybe 12 soldiers.
你有认出任何人吗
Did you recognize anyone?
你为什么要问我那些
Why would you ask me that?
只管回答问题
Just answer the question.
我男朋友弗兰克
My boyfriend Frank.
他被一个人  一个年轻人枪决了
He was executed by, uh, a man, a young man.
乔·布莱克
Joe Blake.
我知道他是谁  我知道他们俩是谁
I know who he is. I know who they both are.
怎样知道
How?
你有认出其他人吗
Did you recognize anyone else?
弗兰克旁边的男人
The man next to Frank.
- 他是谁  - 我不肯定
- Who was he? - I'm not sure.
他看起来很眼熟
He just looked familiar.
好  我要给你看一张脸
Okay. I'm going to show you a face.
如果那是你看到的人  那就告诉我
Tell me if it is the man you saw.
我看的影片  是准备要发生的吗
That film I saw-- is that what's going to happen?
这里的每一部影片都展示了像我们的现实
Each one of these films show a reality like ours
但不是我们的
but not ours.
你在看这些影片的时候知道了很多可怕的事情
Well, you learn an awful lot watching these films.
我们中的一些是一样的
Some of us are just the same--
在现实中是堕落或善良的
rotten or kind in one reality,
在之后变得堕落或善良
rotten or kind in the next,
但是大部分人是不同的
but most people are different,
取决于他们胃里有没有食物
depending on whether they have food in their belly
或他们是饥饿
or they're hungry,
安全还是害怕的
safe or scared.
所以你看这些影片
So you watch these films.
你告诉抵抗组织你看到
You tell the Resistance what you learn--
的人和事
about the people you see and the things.
事情也可能发生在这里
Things that could happen here, too.
那就是为什么
That's why--
那就是为什么纳粹想要这些影片
That's why the Nazis want these films.
不是纳粹  只是老阿道夫
Not the Nazis, just old Adolf.
那疯狂的混蛋太偏执
That demented bastard's too paranoid
去让任何其他人看到那些
to let anyone else see them.
噢  天呐
Oh, God.
等等
Wait.
那是你看到那个男人吗
Was this the man you saw?
在影片里
In the film,
他是被纳粹射杀的
he was shot by the Nazis.
他是游击队的一员  但在这里他是
He was one of the partisans, but here he's--
他是一个纳粹
he's a Nazi.
所以就是那个男人  你认得他
So this was the man. You recognize him.
我觉得是
I think so.
我不知道
I don't know.
你不知道  你不
You don't know. You don't--
你要么认得他们中的一个  要么都不认得
You either recognize him, or you don't.
我不  我不敢肯定
I'm not po-- I'm not positive.
- 快点  想  - 我在努力
- Come on, think! - I'm trying.
你一定在哪里碰到过他
You must have met him somewhere,
在哪个地方见过他
seen him someplace.
不然我们就倒霉了
Then we're screwed.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
那就是你在这里的原因  姑娘
That's the reason you're here, chickie.
在日本人赢得战争的每部影片中
Every film where the Japs won the war,
旧金山迟早会被一枚炸弹清除掉
sooner or later San Francisco is wiped out by an A bomb--
在每一部影片  除了这一部
every one except this one
在这里  这个混蛋作为一个纳粹死在某处的小巷
where this bastard dies as a Nazi in an alley somewhere.
你是在告诉我  如果这个男人可以被找到  那
Are you telling me that if this man can be found, the--
我们可以阻止
we could stop--
是的
Yeah.
我不知道他是谁
I don't know who he is.
我妹妹告诉我这些影片是一个解决方法
My sister said these films were a way out.
是吗
Out?
她告诉我她发现了所有事的答案
She told me she'd found the answer to everything.
是
Yeah.
我看到她
I saw her...
几天之前
a few days ago.
她死了  我知道  我知道她死了
She's dead, I know. I know she's dead.
但她  她没有
But she-- she wasn't.
有没有可能我妹妹在那里仍活着
Is it possible my sister is alive out there
以某种方式
somehow?
我说了你不能问问题
I said you don't ask questions.
他们是感到安全还是害怕
safe or scared.
所以你看这些影片
So you watch these films.
然后告诉抵抗组织你从中获得的信息
You tell the Resistance what you learn--
告诉他们你看到的那些人和事
about the people you see and the things.
那些事儿本来也可能发生在这儿
Things that could happen here, too.
这就是为什么
That's why--
这就是为什么纳粹想要这些影片
That's why the Nazis want these films.
想要它们的不是纳粹  是阿道夫
Not the Nazis, just old Adolf.
那个疯狂的老混蛋太偏执了
That demented bastard's too paranoid
他不愿意让任何人看到这些
to let anyone else see them.
上帝啊
Oh, God.
等下
Wait.
这是那个你看到的人吗
Was this the man you saw?
在影片里
In the film,
他被纳粹射杀
he was shot by the Nazis.
他是游击队的一员  但是在这儿他是
He was one of the partisans, but here he's--
他是一名纳粹
he's a Nazi.
所以就是这个男人  你认出他来了
So this was the man. You recognize him.
我想是的
I think so.
我不知道
I don't know.
你不知道  你不
You don't know. You don't--
你要么认出他来了要么没有
You either recognize him, or you don't.
我不  我不能肯定
I'm not po-- I'm not positive.
- 拜托  回忆一下  - 我正想着呢
- Come on, think! - I'm trying.
你一定在什么地方遇到过他
You must have met him somewhere,
或者在哪儿见过他
seen him someplace.
那我们完蛋了
Then we're screwed.
你什么意思
What are you talking about?
姑娘  这就是你在这儿的原因
That's the reason you're here, chickie.
在每部个日本人赢了战争的影片里
Every film where the Japs won the war,
旧金山早晚都会被原子弹给炸平
sooner or later San Francisco is wiped out by an A bomb--
每一部  除了这部
every one except this one
这部片子里这个混蛋是一名纳粹死在了一个巷子里
where this bastard dies as a Nazi in an alley somewhere.
你是说如果我们能找到这个人的话
Are you telling me that if this man can be found, the--
那我们就能阻止
we could stop--
是的
Yeah.
但我不知道他是谁
I don't know who he is.
我妹妹说这些片子就是我们的出路
My sister said these films were a way out.
出路
Out?
她说这些影片会告诉我们所有事情的答案
She told me she'd found the answer to everything.
是的
Yeah.
我看到她了
I saw her...
在几天之前
a few days ago.
她死了  我知道  我知道她已经死了
She's dead, I know. I know she's dead.
但她  她没死
But she-- she wasn't.
我妹妹现在可能还以某种方式活着吗
Is it possible my sister is alive out there
可能吗
somehow?
我说了你不能问问题
I said you don't ask questions.
你只能回答问题  明白吗
You answer them, got it?
为什么  为什么你这么生我的气
Why? Why are you so angry at me?
因为如果你看到了我所看的东西
Because if you'd seen what I've seen,
你也会一样愤怒
you'd be angry, too.
等一下  等等
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
我也在这些片子里吗
Am I in these films?
为什么  为什么
Why? Why don't--
为什么人们就不能吸取教训呢
Why don't people ever learn?
我在片子里  对吧
I am, aren't I?
你看到了什么
What did you see?
恐惧和暴力
Fear and violence!
这就是我们
It's who we are.
是我们整个悲惨的世界
our whole miserable world,
和像你一样的人  你  你
and people like you, you j-- you j--
- 你最后  - 我最后怎么了
- you end up-- - End up how?
我最后怎么了  我妹妹怎么了
How do I end up? What about my sister?
回答我
Answer me!
关于你的影片
The film of your life--
你不会想知道你最后怎么了的
you don't want to see how it ends.
你好
Woman: Hello.
是魏格纳夫人吗
Is that Mrs. Wegener?
你是哪位
Who is this?
我是户上信介
This is Tagomi Nobusuke.
我去年在斯德哥尔摩的一个商会上
I met the colonel last year in Stockholm
遇到过上校
at a trade convention.
我能和他说话吗
Would it be possible to speak to him?
我丈夫
My husband...
已经死了
is dead.
他
He...
我能问一问发生什么了吗
May I ask what happened?
他们说他开枪自尽了
They say he shot himself.
说他是一个叛徒
He was a traitor.
但你要知道
You must know.
你丈夫是因为努力想把这个世界变得更美好才死的
Your husband died trying to make the world a better place.
那他做到了吗
And did he?
只是努力是不够的  不是吗
Trying is not enough, is it?
这个叫凯拉的怎么样
What about this guy Kera?
他怎么了
What about him?
他在日本政府大厦工作
He works in the Nippon Building.
他是个官员  喜欢日本米酒
He's a bureaucrat with a taste for sake
和关于朱迪·加兰的纪念品
and Judy Garland memorabilia.
好吧  这个呢
All right, this one?
京都  不行  他是一个丝绸商
Kyoto. No, he's a silk merchant.
他已经回到日本
He moved back to Japan.
我但凡有点理智  现在就已经在
If I had any sense, I'd be on a bus
驶向中立区的汽车上了
to the Neutral Zone right now.
那你怎么还在这儿呢
Then why aren't you?
你肯定不缺钱
You must have enough money.
你去过中立区吗
You ever been to the Neutral Zone?
- 没有  - 那你就不会知道
- No. - Then you have no idea
对于一个有教养的人来说
how difficult it would be for a man of culture
在这种龌龊的地方活下去有多难
to survive in an armpit like that.
好吧  我找到一个
All right, I got it.
保罗 凯索拉
Paul Kasoura.
不可能
Yeah, not a chance.
为什么不行  上面说他是个律师
Why not? It says he's a lawyer.
律师的关系网并不广  不是吗
Lawyers are well connected, aren't they?
是  他确实是个律师
Yeah, he's indeed a lawyer,
但我把你做的那个坐牛酋长的护喉
but I sold him and his lovely wife Betty
卖给了他和他可爱的妻子贝蒂
that Sitting Bull gorget you made.
- 所以呢  - 我卖给他的是赝品
- Yeah, so? - So it's a forgery.
现在我们最不需要的
The last thing we need
就是来自凯索拉夫妇的过多关注
is any further attention from the Kasouras.
嘿  你听见我刚才说什么了吗
Hey, did you hear what I just said?
这个人是埃德的最后一次机会
This man's Ed's last chance
也是你的最后一次机会
and yours, too.
过来
Now come on.
这些人是黑社会
Those guys are Yakuza.
是啊  所以我建议我来和他们交涉
Yeah. So I suggest you let me do the talking.
- 又是你  - 我们想见凯索拉先生
- You again. - We need to see Mr. Kasoura.
凯索拉先生不见不期而至的访客
Mr. Kasoura does not receive unannounced visitors,
- 我们已经告诉过你  - 没关系  弗雷德
- and you were told-- - It's all right, Fred.
你想要什么  奇尔丹先生
What is it you want, Mr. Childan?
先生  我们只需要占用你的一点时间
Uh, just a moment of your time, sir.
我保证你不会后悔的
I assure you it will be worth it.
进来吧
Come in.
你是一名刑事辩护律师
You are a criminal defense lawyer,
对吗  凯索拉先生
are you not, Mr. Kasoura?
- 是的  - 我替你找了个案子
- Yes. - I have a case for you,
一个非常重要的案子
a very important one.
你看  这个人的一个朋友
You see, this man has a friend
被诬告攻击皇太子
who has been falsely accused of attacking the Crown Prince.
我们一般不谈及这种事
We do not speak of such things.
当然  当然
Of course. Of course.
但  但他是无辜的
But-- But he is innocent.
我十分确定
I am absolutely certain of it.
这和我有什么关系
What does that have to do with me?
你不明白吗
Well, don't you see?
如果这个攻击皇太子的人
If the wrong man has been charged
是被诬告的
with attacking the Crown Prince,
那这就是最大的误判了
there can be no more serious miscarriage of justice.
如果你能证明这个的话
Now, were you to prove this,
你就会变得很有名  非常出名
it would make you yuumei, very yuumei.
我都是接私人客户  奇尔丹先生
My clients are private, Mr. Childan.
我对声望不感兴趣
I have no interest in fame,
我对给一个攻击了皇太子的人做辩护
and I certainly have no interest
更是一点兴趣都没有
in defending a man accused of attacking the Crown Prince.
请原谅一个白人的肤浅理解
Forgive a white man's shallow understanding,
但是责任和帝国命令比起来
but surely duty to empire dictates--
你们可以走了
You must leave now.
奇  奇尔丹先生
Mr., uh, Mr. Childan,
他八万日元卖给你
he sold you this neck plate...
的那个护喉
for 80,000 yen.
怎么了
Yes?
真是绝妙的价格
An excellent price
- 为这么一件  - 它是假的
- for such a-- - It's a fake.
弗兰克
Frank.
你为什么这么说
Why do you say that?
因为
Well, uh, because, uh...
因为这是我做的
because I made it.
他在撒谎
He's lying.
我没有
No, I'm not.
边缘我还没抛光
I left the edges unpolished.
这里和这里
here and here,
就是为了愚弄像你这种经验丰富的收藏家
to fool even the most experienced collector like you.
很明显这个人被骗了
Uh, this man is clearly deluded.
都是因为他的朋友被指控他的压力太大了
The stress of seeing his friend accused.
我们真诚的道歉  凯索拉先生
Our sincerest apologies, Kasoura-san.
- 我们现在就走  - 你们哪儿都不能去
- We'll leave now. - You're going nowhere.
你错过那条岔道了
You missed the turnoff.
我什么也没错过  我们要去斯托克顿
I didn't miss anything. We're going to Stockton.
阿本德森说了不杀她
Abendsen said not to kill her.
我不在乎阿本德森说了什么
I don't care what Abendsen said.
她已经看到他的脸了
She's seen his face now.
我不同意
Karen: I am not okay with this.
我不需要你的同意  卡伦
I'm not asking your permission, Karen.
你什么时候这么软弱了
Since when did you get so soft?
听起来她醒过来了
Sounds like someone's up.
我们得靠边停下
We got to pull over now.
那是宪兵队
That's Kempeitai.
没关系的  继续开
That's all right. Just keep moving.
操
Shit.
举起手来
Tomaré!
加里
- Karen: Gary--
不
No.
加里  停下  不要
Gary, stop! Don't!
加里
Gary.
操  好吧  坚持住
Oh, shit. All right. Hold--
加里
Gary!
我们得走了
We've got to go now!